=Betrayed Love=
= الحب المغدور =
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
Mr. Shen is to take office today.
السيد شين سيتولى منصبه اليوم.
Come and sit here.
تعال واجلس هنا.
OK.
نعم.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
You came early.
جئت مبكرا.
Yeah, so many people.
نعم ، الكثير من الناس.
Look at her. She's so coquettish.
انظر إليها.  انها غنج جدا.
She is acting like the hostess.
إنها تتصرف مثل المضيفة.
Can this company be lousier?
هل يمكن أن تكون هذه الشركة رديئة؟
A man from a humble background seized his first wife's company.
استولى رجل من خلفية متواضعة على شركة زوجته الأولى.
Then he lives happily with his mistress.
ثم يعيش بسعادة مع عشيقته.
I'll quit tomorrow.
سأستقيل غدا.
Now the Chairman's inauguration ceremony
الآن حفل تنصيب الرئيس
of Guan Group Company begins officially.
بدء تشغيل شركة Guan Group رسميًا.
I, Shen Zhuo, will work tirelessly to make our group a world brand
أنا ، شين تشو ، سأعمل بلا كلل لجعل مجموعتنا علامة تجارية عالمية
and lead Guan Group Company to take it to a new height.
وقيادة شركة Guan Group للارتقاء بها إلى مستوى جديد.
Must we do such a thing, Mr. Tang?
هل يجب أن نفعل مثل هذا الشيء ، سيد تانغ؟
Shen Zhuo is no longer the person you knew.
لم يعد Shen Zhuo الشخص الذي تعرفه.
You've given him many chances.
لقد منحته العديد من الفرص.
He's not worthy of it.
إنه لا يستحقها.
You mustn't be softhearted at this time.
لا يجب أن تكون رقيق القلب في هذا الوقت.
I also need more support and encouragement from you.
أحتاج أيضًا إلى المزيد من الدعم والتشجيع منك.
Today, Guan Group Company officially changed its name to...
اليوم ، غيرت شركة Guan Group اسمها رسميًا إلى ...
Mr. Tang?
السيد.  تانغ؟
Isn't he staying abroad enjoying his autumn years?
ألا يقيم في الخارج مستمتعًا بسنوات الخريف؟
Why did he come back?
لماذا عاد؟
We are screwed.
نحن مشدودون.
This may be our last day in the company.
قد يكون هذا آخر يوم لنا في الشركة.
Don't panic.
لا تُصب بالذعر.
Why are you here, Mr. Tang?
لماذا أنت هنا يا سيد تانغ؟
Today is such an important day for our company.
اليوم هو يوم مهم لشركتنا.
Isn't it too improper for you
أليس هذا غير لائق جدا بالنسبة لك
not to see us, the two honorary chairmen?
ألا ترانا الرئيسان الفخريان؟
Chang Wei, bring a chair to Mr. Tang.
Chang Wei ، أحضر كرسي للسيد Tang.
Mr. Tang came this time
جاء السيد تانغ هذه المرة
to say something to you.
ليقول لك شيئا.
I watched Shen Zhuo
شاهدت شين تشو
grow up in the company.
ينمو في الشركة.
I must admit that
يجب أن أعترف أن
he is really smart and capable.
إنه حقًا ذكي وقادر.
But he repeatedly tried to squeeze his wife out of the company.
لكنه حاول مرارًا وتكرارًا إخراج زوجته من الشركة.
He even tried to kill his beloved several times.
حتى أنه حاول قتل حبيبته عدة مرات.
Guan Xin mortgaged her shares to save the company
رهن Guan Xin أسهمها لإنقاذ الشركة
while Shen Zhuo took this opportunity to seize the control of it.
بينما انتهز Shen Zhuo هذه الفرصة للاستيلاء على السيطرة عليها.
Such a man must not stay in our Guan Group Company.
يجب ألا يبقى مثل هذا الرجل في شركة Guan Group الخاصة بنا.
You did such a good job.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد.
- You got us all fooled. - Plus Guan Peilin's
- لقد خدعتنا جميعًا.  - بلس جوان بيلين
and Guan Xin's, our shares account for over half of the total.
و Guan Xin's ، تمثل أسهمنا أكثر من نصف الإجمالي.
As per the articles of association of the group,
وفقًا للنظام الأساسي للمجموعة ،
Guan Xin will continue to serve as the Chairman of the group.
سيواصل Guan Xin العمل كرئيس للمجموعة.
Now are you aware of it?
الآن هل أنت على علم بذلك؟
I didn't take anything away from my home
لم آخذ أي شيء من منزلي
because I would come back again.
لأنني سأعود مرة أخرى.
You have only yourself to blame
ليس عليك سوى إلقاء اللوم على نفسك
for all these consequences.
لكل هذه العواقب.
It was Xu Jing's idea.
كانت فكرة شو جينغ.
She planned everything.
لقد خططت كل شيء.
Honey, my darling.
عزيزتي عزيزتي.
I have been possessed.
لقد كنت ممسوسًا.
When she worked as the accountant, she incited me
عندما عملت محاسبًا ، حرّضتني
trying to use me to kill you and replace you.
تحاول استخدامي لقتلك واستبدالك.
Do you still remember our quarrel
هل ما زلت تتذكر شجارنا
in the parking lot?
في موقف للسيارات؟
She caused it! She's been pestering me.
تسببت في ذلك!  لقد كانت تضايقني.
She is the culprit!
هي الجاني!
She is out of her mind!
لقد فقدت عقلها!
She has lost her marbles!
لقد فقدت رخامها!
It's all her fault.
كل هذا خطأها.
I beg you, Guan Xin.
أتوسل إليك يا جوان شين.
Can we start all over again?
هل يمكننا البدء من جديد؟
I can leave the company.
يمكنني ترك الشركة.
We can start a new happy life living together.
يمكننا أن نبدأ حياة سعيدة جديدة نعيش معًا.
OK?
نعم؟
Is this also your stalling tactics?
هل هذه أيضًا تكتيكات المماطلة الخاصة بك؟
You don't have a chance now.
ليس لديك فرصة الآن.
Shen Zhuo never struck me as a person
لم يذهلني شين تشو أبدًا كشخص
who would fall to his knees and beg for mercy.
الذي كان يسقط على ركبتيه ويتوسل الرحمة.
I have told you
لقد قلت لك
he only loves himself.
يحب نفسه فقط.
As long as he can live on,
طالما أنه يستطيع العيش ،
his self-esteem and emotions
احترامه لذاته وعواطفه
can all be abandoned.
يمكن التخلي عنها جميعا.
What does it have to do with you?
ما علاقة ذلك بك؟
This is about Guan Xin and me!
هذا عن Guan Xin وأنا!
When you pushed me to the ground
عندما دفعتني إلى الأرض
and caused me to miscarry,
وتسبب لي في إجهاض ،
you just looked like this.
لقد بدوت هكذا للتو.
From the moment I fell off the cliff,
من لحظة سقوطي من على الجرف
I broke off all relations with you.
لقد قطعت كل العلاقات معك.
Honey. Guan Xin.
عسل.  جوان شين.
Stop listening to them, OK?
توقف عن الاستماع إليهم ، حسنًا؟
I still love you.
ما زلت أحبك.
Since you didn't die,
منذ ان لم تموت
we'll die together.
سنموت معا.
Xin!
شين!
Guan Xin!
غوان شين!
Guan Xin, I am at fault.
جوان شين ، أنا المخطئ.
I was too selfish.
لقد كنت أنانيًا جدًا.
I was desperate for love.
كنت بحاجة ماسة للحب.
I thought I would be very happy by making him mine.
اعتقدت أنني سأكون سعيدًا جدًا بجعله ملكي.
I didn't expect I would lose more.
لم أكن أتوقع أن أفقد المزيد.
No matter what the result is,
مهما كانت النتيجة ،
I just want to try my best to offer you an explanation.
أريد فقط أن أبذل قصارى جهدي لأقدم لك شرحًا.
Though you are also a victim,
على الرغم من أنك ضحية أيضًا ،
I still can't make myself forgive you.
ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أسامحك.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
لا أتوقع منك أن تسامحني.
I broke up your family.
لقد فرقت عائلتك.
I was too ridiculous.
كنت سخيفة جدا.
Maybe I will never have my own children in my life.
ربما لن يكون لدي أطفالي في حياتي.
This is the divine punishment for my immoral love.
هذا هو العقاب الإلهي لحبي الفاسد.
This is the price I must pay.
هذا هو الثمن الذي يجب أن أدفعه.
(Police)
(شرطة)
(Shen Zhuo was sentenced to 15 years in prison for illegal detention,)
(حُكم على شين تشو بالسجن 15 عامًا بتهمة الاحتجاز غير القانوني ،)
(attempted intentional homicide and misappropriation of funds.)
(محاولة القتل العمد واختلاس الأموال).
(Yang Zhe was sentenced to 13 years in prison for robbery, extortion,)
(حكم على يانغ زهي بالسجن 13 عامًا بتهمة السرقة والابتزاز)
(illegal use of eavesdropping and stealing special-purpose equipment.)
(استخدام غير قانوني للتنصت وسرقة معدات الأغراض الخاصة.)
(Xu Jing was sentenced to four years and six months in prison)
(حكم على شو جينغ بالسجن أربع سنوات وستة أشهر)
(for attempted intentional homicide and illegal detention.)
(لمحاولة القتل العمد والاحتجاز غير القانوني.)
(Guan Peilin was sentenced to one year and six months in prison)
(حُكم على غوان بيلين بالسجن لمدة عام وستة أشهر)
(for the crime of illegal detention.)
(عن جريمة الاحتجاز غير القانوني).
(Two years later)
(بعد سنتين)
(After all this was over,)
(بعد كل هذا انتهى)
(we started a new life.)
(بدأنا حياة جديدة).
(Clothes Salesman) Wherever you are, we are all friends.
(بائع ملابس) أينما كنت ، فنحن جميعًا أصدقاء.
Could you follow our accounts?
هل يمكنك متابعة حساباتنا؟
The old rules of our streaming booth.
القواعد القديمة لكابينة البث لدينا.
(Guan Peilin initiated the live commerce of the company,)
(بدأ Guan Peilin التجارة الحية للشركة ،)
(which turned out to be a huge success.)
(والذي حقق نجاحًا كبيرًا).
Then this one and this one, OK?
ثم هذا واحد وهذا واحد ، حسنًا؟
All right.
حسنا.
(By her own efforts,)
(من خلال جهودها الخاصة ،)
(Mengran opened a personal studio.)
(افتتح منجران استوديوًا شخصيًا).
(Yang Zhe also wrote to me)
(كتب لي يانغ زهي أيضًا)
(and said he was a model inmate)
(وقال إنه كان نزيلًا نموذجيًا)
(and was applying for commutation.)
(وكان يتقدم بطلب تخفيف.)
(As for my husband Shen Zhuo,)
(أما بالنسبة لزوجي شين تشو ،)
(he is enjoying a peaceful life now.)
(إنه يتمتع بحياة هادئة الآن).
(I heard someone say that marriage is not rosy)
(سمعت أحدهم يقول أن الزواج ليس وردية)
(and it contains many hardships.)
(وفيه كثير من المصاعب).
(Although two people originally loved each other,)
(على الرغم من أن شخصين كانا يحبان بعضهما البعض في الأصل)
(marriage would change the prudent way they treat each other.)
(سيغير الزواج الطريقة الحكيمة التي يعاملون بها بعضهم البعض).
(Therefore, it is not hard to understand)
(لذلك ، ليس من الصعب فهمه)
(that tension and discomfort may occur between them.)
(قد يحدث هذا التوتر وعدم الراحة بينهما.)
(But I think that no matter what the situation is,)
(لكنني أعتقد أنه بغض النظر عن الوضع ،)
(as long as a couple face the tenderness and challenges of the world together,)
(طالما يواجه الزوجان حنان وتحديات العالم معًا ،)
(marriage will always be rosy.)
(سيكون الزواج وردية دائمًا).
(If all this had not happened,)
(إذا لم يحدث كل هذا)
(our life would have been very happy.)
(كانت حياتنا سعيدة للغاية).
(The End)
(النهاية)